Guide to the San Francisco Bay Task Force 1994 Records
Department of Special Collections
San Francisco Bay Task Force 1994 records
1990-1996
Stanford University Archives SC 538
San Francisco Bay Task Force 1994
5.5 linear feet
Stanford University. Libraries. Dept. of Special Collections and University Archives.
Correspondence, memoranda, agreements, guidelines, newsletters, and other records pertaining to ticket sales, marketing, media coverage, negotiations for security arrangements, volunteers, and other aspects of the games. One file pertains to the Task Force's grants to underprivileged soccer youth organizations, following the World Cup games.
Access
Collection is open for research; materials must be requested at least 24 hours in advance of intended use.
Acquisition Information
Gift of the San Francisco Bay Task Force 1994, 1997.
Biography / Administrative History
The San Francisco Bay Task Force assisted in the promotion of the World Cup soccer games held at Stanford Stadium in 1994.
Scope and Content of Collection
Correspondence, memoranda, agreements, guidelines, newsletters, and other records pertaining to ticket sales, marketing, media coverage, negotiations for security arrangements, volunteers, and other aspects of the games. One file pertains to the Task Force's grants to underprivileged soccer youth organizations, following the World Cup games.
Indexing Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the library's online public access catalog.
Stanford University. Stadium.; Soccer--Tournaments--United States.; World Cup (Soccer)--United States.
Container List
- World Cup Tickets 1994 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- World Cup- Bid Supporters (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Government Resources (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Golf (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Insurance (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Protocol Gifts (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Newsletter (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Equipment (Box 1, Folder 8)
- City Hall 9/8 - 10:30 am (Box 1, Folder 9)
- World Net / USIA / VOA (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Cavalli and Cribbs (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Marketing Group (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Security (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Training Sites (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Hospitality (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Hotels (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Volunteer Coordinator (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Resources - Volunteer (Box 1, Folder 18)
- World Cup Sponsors (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Uniform Distribution Center and Venue Motor Pool (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Host Committee Store - Intercontinental Sports Promotions (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Tickets - Public and Premier (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Line of Credit (Box 2, Folder 2)
- LOOK (Box 2, Folder 3)
- World Cup Teams1994 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Host Committee Co-Chair (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Protocol and Gifts (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Other Venues - General (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Other Venues - Host and Venue Executive Directors (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Palo Alto Traffic Cost (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Media Center (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Soccer Legacy Applications1996 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Venue Bid Process (Box 3, Folder BN 1)
- Host Committee Agreement (Box 3, Folder BN 2)
- Host Committee Guidelines (Box 3, Folder BN 3)
- Host Committee Duties - Entertainment, Government Liaison, Protocol, Security, Volunteers, Speakers, Publicity, Merchandise (Box 3, Folder BN 44)
- San Francisco Bay Host Committee XV FIFA World Cup - Information Reference Guide (Box 3, Folder BN 5)
- Stanford University Stadium Negotiations, Liability and Volunteer Workers' Compensation Insurance (Box 4, Folder BN 6)
- Marketing, Licensing and Fund Raising (Box 4, Folder BN 7)
- World Cup Draw, Tickets, The Competition, Press Conferences (Box 4, Folder BN 8)
- Pele Breakfast - Postrio Restaurant - San Francisco, CA - San Jose Welcomes World Cup 1994 (Box 4, Folder BN 9)
- World Cup Press Articles February 1990 through December 1993 (Box 4, Folder BN 10)
- World Cup Press Articles January 1994 through August 1994 (Box 5, Folder BN 11)
- Hotel Reservations - Accommodations (Box 5, Folder BN 12)
- World Cup USA Official Identification Standards Manual 1994 (Box 5, Folder BN 13)